const DATA = [
    {
        question: 'Which ingredient is a common and harmful sweetener 
        found in almost all foods containing added sugar?',
        answers: [
            'High-fructose corn syrup',
            'Honey',
            'Fresh fruits',
            'Stevia'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'High-fructose corn syrup'
    },
    {
        question: 'How much sugar should you eat per day?',
        answers: [
            '200 calories per day',
            '100-150 calories per day',
            '500 calories per day',
            '1000 calories per day'
        ],
        correctAnswer = '100-150 calories per day'
    },
    {
        question: 'Prolonged high blood glucose levels can lead to?',
        answers: [
            'Diabetes',
            'Heart attack',
            'Arrythmia',
            'Stroke
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Diabetes"
    },
    {
        question: 'Which is a sign of iodine deficiency?',
        answers: [
            'Hyperactivity',
            'Goiter',
            'Hair gain',
            'Feeling hot'
        ],
        correctAnswer = 'Goiter'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which is an excellent source of iodine?',
        answers: [
            'Blueberries',
            'Seaweed',
            'Banana',
            'Plain rice'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Seaweed'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which measurement is used to access your ideal weight?',
        answers: [
            'Chest circumference',
            'Body Mass Index',
            'Water intake',
            'Caloric intake'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Body Mass Index'      
    },
    {
        question: 'What is Alzheimer’s disease?',
        answers: [
            'A condition where blood vessels are narrowed or blocked leading 
            to pain in the muscle and valves.',
            'An irreversible brain disorder that destroys your memory and 
            thinking skills and eventually, not able to carry out simple tasks.', 
            'A disease that affects the blood vessels in the brain.',
            'A disorder in the nervous system that causes tremor.'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'An irreversible brain disorder that destroys your memory and 
            thinking skills and eventually, not able to carry out simple tasks.'
    },
    {
        question: 'Omega-3 fatty acids play an important role in the prevention 
        of Alzheimer’s disease. Where are they found?',
        answers: [
            'Rice',
            'Fatty fish',
            'Carbonated drinks',
            'Dairy'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Fatty fish'
    },
    {
        question: 'Cholesterol is required for cellular production. What are the \
        two types?',
        answers: [
            'CDL and BDL',
            'HDL and LDL',
            'GDL and BDL',
            'None of the above'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'HDL and LDL'
    },
    {
        question: 'Why is it important to monitor and control your cholesterol level?',
        answers: [
            'High level of bad cholesterol can lead to a clot and eventually cause a 
            heart attack of stroke.',
            'High level of bad cholesterol can lead to insulin resistance.',
            'Low level of cholesterol can decrease energy level.', 
            'Low level of cholesterol can lead to ADHD.'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'High level of bad cholesterol can lead to a clot and eventually cause a 
            heart attack of stroke.'
    }
];